Thank you for watching
ME
Art Games
me
This time, we divided into three teams and played a game of painting.
Let's play the next game! Calculator on my back
me
Everyone wears a t-shirt and write a picture of the theme on the back of the next person, and ask them to tell what was written.
After 20 seconds, Mr. Himura will follow you like this, and then he'll slap you like this.
First, the team writes. - Wait a minute.
I'm good at capturing the right moment.
I'm good at capturing the characteristics.
Let's start!
Four, three, two, one.
I wrote on the back of the next one, anticipating the picture I felt on my back and telling the next one, and the subject reached Sakaguchi.
Why didn't it look like that?
Why that shape?
I'm sorry.
What the hell?
Are you saying it's okay?
You're being selfish.
Why is it... why does it look different on my back than it does on yours?
I don't get it.
The power of decipherment.
Do your best.
Read it.
How is the subject conveyed?
please show me your bouquet, bouquet, bouquet, bouquet, bouquet, bouquet, bouquet, bouquet...
I really didn't understand what was written in your spring, Katatsumuri.
I'm sorry.
Is that what you called me?
eyes
It's great, isn't it?
What did you write on it?
It looks like eyes.It looks like an eye.
What's written on it?
Was that a snail?
It's funny.
It's funny... he says "Katasumuri".
But you wrote "katatsumuri".
Butterfly.
It's almost as if you copied it.
It's a butterfly.
So that's why it's one-snail.
And it's an eye.
It's more like a snail.
The one-snail in the mural.
It's amazing how the one-snail comes out once.
You communicated one... 3 points.
Next, Team Inoue takes on the challenge
Let's go, Mr. Himura, let's get started!
Let's start!
You've got 20 seconds.
Great!
Eight, seven, six, five seconds.
This is mystery 3
One, love. End.
I'm going to focus all my attention on the back, decipher the message to the next member's back, and pass it on to the next member's back.
End of love
This is interesting.
I wonder how this picture, the subject of this riddle, is conveyed to the next member's back.
Now, Kanagawa, please tell us what you drew.
Frog
Oh my gosh, I can't tell if it's a frog, a bear, or a rabbit!
What did you draw?
I drew a frog too.
This one's really funny.
This guy is so funny!
Seriously, he's got a nice face.
What did you draw?Let's see what you've drawn!
A bear.
Right here... but it's getting the message across.
No, I told them what you didn't want me to tell them.
A frog.
Your style has changed a lot here.
The shape is similar, but...
The style has changed completely.
It's completely different.
Now, Lilia, what is it?
Mountains.
A mountain.
I don't know what this is.
I don't know what this was.
Frogs.
Frogs!
Frogs are here.
Maybe it's a frog and it's coming to this point.
It's connected. It's connected.
This one's not even on the team.
I don't see the one we just saw.
There's the guy from before.
Is this what this game is supposed to be?
This is the second one from the start, and this is the one you don't hit, and it's zero points.
It's the eye of the frog.
Frog eye.
Frog's eye.
Yumiki.
Yuki, what is this?
It is a whale.
A whale!
It's not good to trace.
I don't know what to trace.
I tend to be a frog in this game.You tend to be a frog, this game.
Yes, the game frogs.
That's why
Zero points.
Surprisingly, I didn't get the message here.
me Next, Team Ikeda tried to play, but the turtle turned into a lion.
No one got the message and it stood out.
Let's play the next game.
me 5 players draw a picture of a theme, one stroke at a time.
Each person has to complete the picture 10 times, but there is a hidden member among the five who is writing without knowing the theme.
The guessing team gets 5 points if they can find out who is writing the theme, and each team gets 5 points if they can hide the person who doesn't know the theme.
If you don't complete it, you're out. If you write too well, the unknown person will stand out, and you'll be found out.
That's right. That's the hard part.
First of all, the team writers and the team-i's are competing against each other.
First of all, genre, genre, creatures, creatures.
It's a very broad genre.
And then the team members check the subject, and there's one member who has a blank sheet of paper.
And then we're going to play a game where we're going to reveal the theme only to our audience, so let's see who the blank member is.
Let's start with a stroke of the pen, and we'll do two rounds.
That's it.
I'm done.
What should I do?
I guess the genre is "living creatures.
Oh!
Please complete this in two weeks.
What?
There are some members here who don't know the right answer.
Oh!
I can do it with one stroke.
Well, well, well. One stroke will do.
What?
Well, it's kind of like an image.
That's the second round I didn't know about. Here comes the second round.
I don't know, I don't know...
He clearly wrote something.I obviously wrote something. Oh, it's just a stroke.
Oh, really? Well, that's all right.
Who doesn't know? It's a guessing game.
They're all so bold.
So many strokes!
What's this?
It's a little...
It's got a Sakaguchi quality to it.
I seriously can't tell at this point.
What's this?
Mr. Himura doesn't know either.
I don't know.
If Mr. Himura doesn't recognize it, he's out.
Someone might have to die to finish it.
A stroke of bad luck.
What's that?
It's a plum tree.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Ah!
Yes, it's over.
If this creature does not get the message, he is immediately disqualified.
Nimura's answer is
What is it?
Sorry if I'm wrong.
I'm sorry if I'm wrong.
Mantis.
Correct.
Oh, wait, that was close.
No, that was a close one.
That was a close one.
You'd think they'd have closed the door by now.
That's dangerous!
It's guessing time from here! Who among you put the brush in the sickle cut without knowing the subject?
Now then, Inoue, who is doing this without knowing it?
It's Mr. Seimya Rei.Mr. Seimyaray.
I see.
Seimya.
The Inoue team's prediction is Seimya.
Is this miracle a know-it-all?
Raise your hand if you didn't know and wrote it down, please.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Is it absolutely so or is this
I don't know what the second one means either, because it's like that half circle, and it's quite strange.
I thought it'd be great if he wrote a leaf, Akamura, but if he writes a plant, then it must be meat.
I honestly thought it was a shrimp at first.
I thought it was a shrimp at first, but now I'm thinking it's more like a sickle-cutter.
I wanted to write something about this... but...
I wanted to write about this part, but I thought that if this voice entered my mind, I would understand.
The first one is too big, and the second one is too big.
When I said "creature" I could only think of animals, so I wondered if I'd be able to write "worm" in the right way.
Masamiya, when you first drew the one-sided line, I thought it might be a persimmon.
I couldn't figure it out, so I just went to the ground, and then this came out, and at some point I thought, "Well, this is something different.
I thought it was about sake...
I'm not sure if that's going to come up because he knows how to cut the sickle.
I'm sorry to say that I don't want to be a part of this, so here's 5 points for Team Inoue.
5 points to Team Inoue!
Next, Team Iida and Team Kaki will play each other.
Now then, I'll announce the genre.
Genre
Vehicle
Wow, but if we get a unique one...
Among these five, there is only one member whose theme is blank.
This time, please guess the blank member without knowing what the theme is.
Here we go.
Here you go.
Ho!
It's bad if I'm not right.
Maybe it's a "make or break" line.
Here you go, Yamashita.Here you go, Yamashita.
Oh, my God.
Hmm?
Oh...
What's that?
What?
It's like the same kind of green.
It's the same little green.
Maybe I missed it.
Oh, wow.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, it's all of a sudden.
That's a good sign.
It really hit me.
I see.
Yes, yes.
Direction of travel.
I wrote down the direction of travel.
Entering the second lap.
But you know what?
On the other hand...
If you write it down right, you won't know who writes it.
That's right.
You're good.
You're good... with just one stroke.
You can do it.
I don't have anything else to write.
Maybe you're right.
You probably already know.
If that's it, we all know it.
We all know it now.
Ha-ha-ha!
I'd like to write something like that, wouldn't you?
Yamashita and the rest...
Yes, yes
It's possible that you're writing this even if you don't know about it.It's possible that I'm writing this even if I don't know this already, so yes...
It's a genre. It's a vehicle.
What am I doing with that?
I don't know how to say this.
It's already gone that way.
That's it.
What the hell is this thing? If you don't get the message, you're disqualified.
What's your answer?
Mr. Himura, please.
A ship.
Correct.
Good.
Why did you use that one today?
I thought it could be a yacht or a cruiser.
What's that round thing?
That.
Right there.
I thought it was... a yacht... just because I suddenly thought it was a yacht.
Who was the one who wrote the subject, pretending to know what it was about?
What do you think the teams will do?
Seino
Shiori
Shiori Kubo
The second Kubo
Kubo, who drew a bold horizontal line at the bottom of her brush.
Raise your hand if you didn't know you were writing!
Ahhh...
Yamashita Yamashita, right?
Yamashita... right?
I thought so too.
I thought it was Yamashita. He was deliberately shifting it.
When I first saw the trapezoid, I thought it was a coffee cup.
Why a ride? An amusement park?
I thought it was a twist.
Is that what you meant?
That's not what I meant.No, it wasn't.
I thought he got away with writing the same tiny thing because I didn't recognize it anymore.
I wrote the coffee cup next to it.
I'm not going any more... that's the second time around... and it's a boat...
I'm not going any more!
I'd like to be a one-man show.
The trapezoid's a ship, too. You have to be the deceiver.
You fooled me.
That last one, the Kawasaki, was that a fire? A fire. That's where he wrote it.
Like this.
I don't think they'll use this trick.
Team Inoue draws, Team Ikeda deduces. The theme here is "Yakiniku.
Nagi.
Yes! But Kanagawa, the team that knew, fooled us all and won 5 points for Team Inoue.
Now for the next game, Inoue-san!
The next game is "Eye Mask Nut Heaven".
Here you go!
Draw a picture of the theme with an eye mask and guess what you drew.
The time limit is 2 minutes.
First, the team draws a picture.
Draw with blindfolds on.
Yes, I see.
Guess without blindfold
Nice!
It's impossible to guess without looking!
Very good, very good!
Let's start the eye mask illustration message game!
The one who draws first has the advantage.
Okay, let's get him out of there.
Ferris wheel.
Amusement park.
Correct! Correct! Correct!
Correct.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes YesYes, sir. - No, no, no.
No, no, no.
Keep it closed.
Yes, sir.
Leave the bottom open.
Oh, no.
You'd better write it down and get it out of here.
Come on.
Thirty seconds.
It's done.
Let's get it out.
Mike car
Genetic car.
Yes. Correct.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
Cute!
Cute.
Yes. - Yes.
It's done.
Please do it, please do it, please do it, please do it, please do it, please do it, please do it
Toilet box
Correct.
Yes!
That was fast.
Quick! Quick! Quick!
Quick.
Early. - Early.
early (i.e. early)
earlyThat was fast.
Even with blindfolds, everyone's pretty good at it.
Here.
Here we go.
Wow.
Bag.
Let's see...
The stash.
Stylish.
Girls
Pass
Yes
Cute
Cute.
Lovely.
Well, time is running out... 30 seconds to go.
Kegucka.
That's right.
That's great.
LOL
tunnel tunnel
road road road
pass pass pass
This is bad.
OK
that's too bad
That was a close one.
I didn't have time.
Here are the two I passed.
Teams write four correct answers for 12 extra points.12 points added for 4 correct team-written questions.
Next up is Team E's challenge!
Let's get started!
Let's go!
Cat
Horse.
What is it?
Uh... uh... sheep.
Dog. Cat.
Yes, that's right, a dog.
Here we go!
It took me a while, though.
Doraemon.
Correct!
Doraemon!
30 seconds elapsed
Baseball
Correct.
Baseball.
That's great!
You're good.
Mickey.
Bear.
That's good.
That's good. That's good. That's good.
Okay, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
One minute elapsed.
Wait a minute. Kendo, kendo, kendo.
Tennis, fencing, haunted house.
I don't know. I don't know.
40 seconds elapsed.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
We have to move fast or we won't get any closer.
You were right about the mask.
Now, last 10 seconds... eight, seven, six...
Pitcher, pitcher, pitcher!Pitcher, pitcher, pitcher.
Yes, sir. Correct.
Ten seconds left.
Nine. Eight.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Five. Four.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Two. One.
Okay, you can hold it down.
Boxing.
I'm sorry.
No, it's too hard.
Passed the Smote Running Wide
Team Inoue 18 extra points for 6 correct answers.
I can't do it, I can't do it, I have to pass!
Finally, Team Ikeda takes the challenge!
Pass!
The team used up all the time with a series of passes and ended up with 6 points.
The winning team
The winner of the closely contested game tournament was...
Let's see who won the Himura-san 1st Art Game Tournament!
Keiichi Inao with 40 points
Now, Captain Inoue of Team Inoue!
Here you go!
The winner is Keiichi Inao!
The winner!
You did it!
What a trophy!
I didn't say you were good, did I?
No.
It's not about who's good.
It was a fun game.
But, you know, people started wearing T-shirts in the middle of the game.
Every time you walked around, there was a dumbass written on it.
That's right.
It wasn't so much a game of backhandedness as it was a game of...It was more of a game of back-to-back communication.
It was more a game of becoming a frog.
The jacket photo of Ohitorisama Tengoku is completed.
Three Dance Battles Against Demons
The next gachinko battle begins!
Trust your friends and grab the victory!
Hello, my name is Miyu Matsuo.
My latest hobby is roasting marshmallows on the kitchen stove.
Sometimes they burn, but they are delicious!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Next Episode
Gachinko Battle